(With a light drizzle falling,)
(it's early morning in Itaewon.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Kyoung Pyo.
Today, you look...
- gorgeous. - Gorgeous?
- Is something wrong? - There's something...
He lost weight.
- Me? - It looks like you lost weight.
- Really? - Yes, he lost some weight.
- But I haven't changed. - Hello.
- Hello, Eun I. - Hello.
Has anything happened?
Not much happened.
- Are we getting something? - What?
- Are we not getting anything? - I made an order.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you, sir.
I got some Pu'erh tea.
- I want some Pu'erh tea too. - Me too.
Me too.
- Pu'erh tea. - Pu'erh tea.
- Pu'erh tea. - Pu'erh tea for everyone.
- May I check your microphone? - Sure.
(Checking BIBI's microphone)
One of them fell off. I was fiddling with it.
What are you wearing underneath?
- Underneath? - I see.
(There's another layer.)
It's my underwear...
Your underwear?
- This... - You're wearing it on the outside?
These are shorts I usually sleep in.
But you wore them outside?
- This morning, - You can have...
I overslept.
You can have that conversation in front of us?
I didn't think they were underwear.
I thought it was a fashion statement.
When Hyeong Seo wears it, it looks like fashion.
Send some to Eun I, will you?
It's okay. She wears these shorts at home,
and she's wearing them underneath.
She was running late.
I ran out of the house in a hurry.
(During their underwear talk, the Pu'erh tea got fully steeped.)
It looks like something came up with our guest today.
What happened?
The person who promised to join us had...
- something come up. - I see.
- It's nothing serious. - Then who's coming today?
Are our friends coming?
- I'll stand here. - Hello.
Hello.
I'm very grateful to one of them.
He was invited on short notice...
- around 10pm last night. - He was invited on short notice.
- That short? - Yes.
If there are two guests,
let's guess who came at the last minute.
Shall we guess who it was?
(Who will be the two friends?)
- Hello. - Gosh, hello.
(Hello)
(Everyone is happy to see them.)
- Jung Ha Jun. - My gosh.
(Today's guests, Ye Na and Jun Ha)
- My goodness. - I see.
I immediately guessed which one it was.
- Jun Ha. - Hello, everyone.
- Wipe off your sweat. - You're right.
(Which one was invited yesterday?)
My goodness.
It's Ye Na.
Have a seat.
We called you at 10pm last night.
- Thank you for coming. - Sure.
- Have you been well, Jun Ha? - Of course.
It's good to see you.
I had no idea.
- You had no idea? - No.
- Really? - I had no idea at all.
- Not at all? - No.
Seriously?
- It's Ye Na. - Hello.
(Dancing automatically)
(Everyone dances to "Catch Catch.")
- Seriously. - Thank you.
- We have Ye Na with us. - Have a seat.
I'm sure that everyone can tell.
Ye Na and Jun Ha aren't related at all.
Of course not.
- Between them... - But our names rhyme.
That must be it.
- "Ye Na and Jun Ha?" - He's right.
- Ye Na and Jun Ha. - That makes sense.
- Their names rhyme. - As I said earlier,
we had invited Ye Na in advance.
Right.
- We called him at the last minute. - It was raining lightly,
so I was having a drink.
I had this gut feeling...
that something was wrong when I got the call.
At that hour, most people call you out for drinks.
- The director called him. - Right.
He asked me what I was doing tomorrow.
Why is he asking all of a sudden?
I had plans next evening.
I said that I had work only in the evening.
He said, "That's perfect."
I didn't understand what was perfect.
(I found the person I was looking for.)
Thank you so much for inviting me.
- Thank you very much. - It's my pleasure.
Do you know BIBI well?
- The two of you... - We're very close.
She featured on my debut song.
- Really? - Right.
(They even performed together for Ye Na's debut.)
We met through a variety show. We've spent time together...
since then.
We see each other often in private.
- Really? - Yes.
BIBI has a bold personality.
I tend to think a lot,
and I can't put things into action.
- I hesitate a lot. - Let's go.
- But she's a woman of action. - Let's do it.
- She leads you to do it right away. - Right.
- So we get along very well. - Yes.
You get along really well, and you have great chemistry.
But from her agency's point of view,
- Right. - when Ye Na hangs out with BIBI...
- Because I might influence her. - Exactly.
(Because I might influence her...)
- One thing is for sure. - She's the dark IU.
That sounds a little harsh.
That you'll influence her.
Even my little sister's agency doesn't like it...
when she hangs out with me.
I can understand from the agency's point of view.
Especially for idol singers, BIBI seems...
(Upset)
- Actually, I'm very wholesome. - Exactly.
- When you get to know her, - I'm very wholesome.
BIBI is actually not like that.
- Right. - I agree.
(Sweet and innocent)
- But there's "gang" in it. - Most people think...
- Gang. - Right, it's gang.
There is nothing to worry about. BIBI is a good person...
from what I've seen.
(Did you hear that?)
She is acting cute in front of the camera.
- Please order something to drink. - Okay.
Everyone is drinking something hot.
- Please get them a drink. - One iced Americano, please.
Both of you are in sync with me.
- Both Eun I and Jun Ha. - Right.
We've worked together for a long time.
- We used to be at the same agency. - Right.
We were in the same office.
Since "Truth Game..."
- that you hosted together, - "Truth Game."
isn't this your first time on a show together?
That's right.
This show is quite similar.
- To "Truth Game?" - Yes.
This is a little different.
(Teasing)
That was filmed in a studio. We're filming outdoors this time.
Right, it's different.
- I guess it's different. - Do you know Kyoung Pyo well?
- A long time ago, we... - We know each other.
- We filmed a sitcom together. - That's right.
To become a model on "Infinite Challenge,"
- he had lost a lot of weight. - Right.
He was extremely sensitive.
When he played the bumpkin character?
- The bumpkin character. - He was Jung Bumpkin.
It was when he played Jung Bumpkin.
Wasn't it when you got dust stuck in here?
Jae Seok used to dust it off with a brush.
- The lines were very deep. - Right.
(Feeling nostalgic)
Where are we going today?
I don't know. They will tell us where to go.
Is that so?
- They'll tell us where to go. - I see.
What is today's theme?
Today's theme is...
- "Why Can't You Order?" - What?
"Why Can't You Order?" What do you mean?
Everything must be in English because we're in Itaewon.
What?
Are we trying food from other countries?
We might be eating something unusual or exotic.
Maybe an international specialty.
Or it could be an omakase.
Forget about what you like.
Eat whatever I give you. That's a possibility.
Shall we take a look at it?
(Why can't they order for themselves?)
We will play this 1 by 1.
I haven't seen it in a long time.
- These will be clues. - I see.
Please listen up.
This is the first one.
(First location: On-site reaction hint)
(Swoosh)
What? There's no end to it.
- There's no end to what? - "What? There's no end to it."
- The sound earlier... - Did you hear that swish sound?
Wasn't it the sound of turning pages?
(Tape 1, some kind of ordering system involving paper?)
No, it was the sound of slurping noodles.
Jun Ha, you know exactly what that sound is.
It didn't sound like slurping noodles.
(Pouting and sulking)
- You made a mistake. - This is getting interesting.
I should stay away from them.
You're very pouty today.
(Very happy, very pouty)
We speak our minds freely to each other.
I know.
I've seen it very often.
But it's been a while, so I'm happy to see it again.
(Happy)
This is the second one. Listen carefully.
(Second location: On-site reaction hint)
(Scribbling sounds?)
- Is this right? - The resemblance is incredible.
"Is this right? The resemblance is incredible."
- It was a scratching sound. - It sounded like...
- A drawing? - Maybe it's a pencil...
- making that scratchy sound. - Right.
It could be a shop where they do caricatures.
(Tape 2, a shop related to caricatures?)
The third and final one.
(Third location: On-site reaction hint)
(Tapping)
(A sound of a machine?)
What? Is it mind reading?
It sounds like someone typing a message.
- Right. - After typing a message...
"Is it mind reading?"
When something comes out with a whirring sound...
What could it be?
(They have no clue what the third place could be.)
- This is just a feeling. - I like this kind of deduction.
- What is it? - Feelings are good.
- I think the first one is fake. - Why?
- We haven't even started. - What?
- The tone of the voice was... - Was it too...
"What? There's no end to it."
It sounded a little forced.
Your close friend seems very disappointed.
(- Ye Na... - BIBI.)
- I don't think you caught it right. - "Catch Catch."
("Catch Catch" is a big failure.)
Everyone was paying attention to her.
We'll figure it out once we experience it ourselves, right?
- That's obvious. - Right now...
(That's obvious.)
(Coughing out of embarrassment)
Let me explain why.
We have plenty of screen time,
so please refrain from saying the obvious.
(Please refrain from making obvious comments.)
You're an expert on small businesses.
I was setting it all up to talk about that,
but never mind.
(Sulky)
I won't do it anymore.
Let's go and catch, catch.
"Catch Catch."
(They head out to catch the fake place.)
- Long time, no see, Eun I. - It's been a long time.
I haven't been on a show with you for a long time.
- I know. - Right?
I'm very grateful, Jun Ha.
No, the pleasure is mine.
I'm still grateful.
(The best friends are grateful to each other.)
- Ye Na. - E.
- We're here. - By the way...
(What kind of places with difficult orders are waiting for them?)
There are so many places to eat around here.
This place is trendy these days.
- I used to live here. - Really?
- Yes. - My gosh.
There's no way I wouldn't know this place.
This is where Kyoung Pyo used to walk...
- around in shorts. - Right.
(They arrive at a street where Kyoung Pyo used to show up often.)
Can there be clues hidden around here?
Yes, while walking on the street, you might see...
- something on here. - Something could be posted up.
Out of the blue?
(B-Side gave them clues that were hidden all over the place.)
(Property Number 2, pristine condition. Beware of the Mona Lisa.)
Didn't we find it?
(You never know where something will pop up.)
(Do not trust.)
Something completely ridiculous like this.
I haven't been here in a long time.
- In the past, Seok Cheon... - It's where his restaurants were.
- Right. - This is the place.
It used to be this restaurant.
- His entire My Series was here. - Right.
This was basically Seok Cheon's alley.
Seok Cheon's restaurant was somewhere around here.
- My gosh. - His restaurants were everywhere.
I used to come to nightclubs around here all the time.
You did?
- It's raining. - It's raining hard.
- Wait. - Let's get out of the rain.
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
- It's raining without notice. - Over here...
(Where is Jae Seok going?)
- Here... - This is the place.
This is the place.
- Go in quickly. - This is the place.
Let's go in here.
- Suddenly... Jae Seok. - Here are the umbrellas.
Here are the umbrellas.
(Grasshopper Man runs through the wind and rain.)
Jae Seok.
(Wait, here come the umbrellas.)
- Is this the place? - Everyone went inside.
Are we here?
He was getting umbrellas for us.
(They arrived through the wind and rain.)
(What is this place where it's hard to make orders?)
An Indian vegetarian restaurant.
What? An Indian vegetarian restaurant?
- It's Indian vegetarian food. - Indian vegetarian food?
I've had Indian food before,
- but vegetarian food... - It's vegetarian.
(When they go inside the restaurant)
My gosh.
My goodness.
What's this?
(An interior design with a modern vibe)
- The restaurant looks real. - Definitely.
Based on the interior and the vibe,
the restaurant looks real, doesn't it?
Everything is written up there.
"Vegetarian, gluten-free."
(It looks like an ordinary vegetarian restaurant.)
Here's what's important.
When we listened to the tape,
something kept coming out endlessly. Right?
(First location: On-site reaction hint)
(Swoosh)
(What? There's no end to it.)
- Shall we call the owner? - Okay.
(What is something endless with the swoosh sound?)
Sir?
(Someone comes out at the sound of their calling.)
- She's actually Indian. - She's Indian.
Oh, my gosh. What should we say?
- Hello. - Hello, ma'am.
- Are you the interpreter? - Yes.
I see.
Ma'am.
Could you tell us what kind of restaurant this is?
It's an Indian vegetarian restaurant.
At this restaurant,
we have vegan, gluten-free, and vegetarian food on the menu.
Gluten-free? The food must be healthy.
Is it hard to order at this restaurant?
Is everything in Hindi?
We have 200 items on the menu.
- Two hundred? - Two hundred?
- All 200 items are vegetarian? - Yes.
Is that why it's endless?
We opened this restaurant in Korea in 2024.
We started with 200 dishes on our menu.
We added more North Indian food,
more tandoori, and Indo-Chinese menu.
Now we have more than 250 dishes.
(250 menu items on the day of the shoot)
Our signature menu is dosa.
We have other popular items like chana bhatura, onion pakora,
paneer tikka, paneer makhani, vegetable curry,
pani puri, North Indian-style thali...
(Gobi 65, palak paneer, Sichuan noodles, onion dosa, ghee roast,)
(cheese dosa, paneer cheese kathi roll...)
(And there's a lot more.)
India is a very big country with diverse food culture.
Each state has different dishes...
and diversified food habits.
India is a place where you have a lot of vegetarians.
That's how we wanted to showcase...
our food to Korean people.
That's why we added so many on the menu.
There's an Indian restaurant with 200 items on the menu?
If you like Indian food, you must save it.
Sixth Sense crew,
is this place real?
That's incredible.
(They're shocked to hear it.)
There's no way.
- May I see the menu? - Sure.
- With 200 items on the menu... - Please take a look.
It's as big as an old phone book.
It's really thick.
Like an old phone book...
There are images too.
- There are images. - It looks delicious.
(Pick whatever you'd like.)
- There are curries too. - I want some curry.
- There's also tandoori. - There's tandoori.
(They take a look at the menu.)
- There's a lot. - This is...
- There's so much on the menu. - There's a lot.
There are so many items that I don't know what to order.
By the way,
how many chefs do you have at this restaurant?
We have four chefs at this restaurant.
- Four? - And they make all of these?
They make everything on the menu?
(4 chefs make 200 menu items?)
- But... - Our chefs...
(Is this possible?)
No chef would like to make 200 dishes.
- It's exhausting. - Right.
This is impossible.
(It's impossible for 4 chefs to make 200 dishes.)
Kyoung Pyo, is there anything you'd like?
I can't help being suspicious.
Since I'm not a vegetarian, there's nothing I'm craving.
Right.
- Are you a meat lover? - Yes, but...
Ye Na, is there anything you want?
(Let me see.)
Shouldn't we order something that no one would ever order?
You're right.
- We must stay suspicious. - Won't that make them flustered?
If we order something unexpected,
- We haven't tried that approach. - they might not be prepared.
If we order something that no one orders,
- it'd be something unpopular. - Right.
It won't taste so good.
Jae Seok doesn't like trying new food.
- He wants something safe. - I think he's hungry.
(Jae Seok is a picky eater.)
If you recommend us...
a dish, we'll try it.
Sure.
Our signature menu item is dosa.
- Dosa? - We offer 50 types of dosa.
- Dosa? - Yes, dosa.
Our signature menu items are ghee roast...
and family dosa.
- Dosa? - Family dosa.
- I want to try this. - What?
Onion pakora.
- Try it. - Let's order some tandoori.
- Tandoori sounds good. - That sounds good.
All right, go ahead and order it.
(The food is here.)
(Coming up soon)
(Leaving the Sixth Sense members stunned)
(Indian food that looks shocking?)
(The ultimate Indian vegetarian feast is about to appear.)
(You can look forward to it.)
We prepared one more thing for you.
- You prepared something? - Yes, we have one more thing.
- Please bring it out. - Okay, thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Let me say this because Jun Ha is here.
Would they make enough to cover the costs?
Right, that's important.
- You're right. - That's important.
- Would they cover the costs? - It's impossible.
- Ingredient costs... - They offer 200 dishes.
I don't think 4 chefs can make 200 dishes.
If I were them, I'd quit.
- That's what I said. - Right.
Can they memorize all 200 dishes?
That's another question I have.
This might be the key clue.
Wasn't my deduction sharp?
- Could you explain... - No one is listening to you.
(They don't care about what he says.)
It's you guys who aren't listening.
The three of you in the front.
- Did you see his buck teeth? - The three of you in the front.
- Aren't you listening to me? - We are not.
The three of you in the front, you aren't listening to me?
You're the worst.
(Leaving his battered deduction behind)
- Hold on. - My gosh.
- What is it? - Goodness.
They must've prepared something.
(Appearing from somewhere)
(Indian people?)
(They're happy to see them.)
(Who are you?)
- But... - It must be a performance.
- A performance all of a sudden? - Is this what she prepared?
(They start to move to the music.)
- They're not on beat. - Be quiet.
(From here, they're perfectly on beat.)
Are they...
(Suddenly, the vibe turns into Bollywood.)
They're so cute.
(Singing)
That's beautiful.
(Turning swiftly)
They don't look like professional dancers.
I'm sorry, but we have to stay suspicious.
They definitely prepared this for us.
Right.
(The welcoming performance for Sixth Sense crew is over.)
All right.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I don't think they're used to performing.
- I don't think so either. - No.
- They don't always do that. - That's true.
Why does everything look fake?
(The performance looks awkward. Is this place fake?)
The food is here.
(What's that?)
- How can we eat that? - What's that?
Is that...
(The restaurant's signature dish finally appears.)
He brought out a piece of vinyl flooring.
Did you say "vinyl flooring?"
This is family dosa.
- Is it family dosa? - How can we eat that?
It's vinyl flooring.
(Staring)
Thank you, ma'am.
(Dosa which looks like vinyl flooring is laid out on the table.)
- There's more. - What?
(Flinching)
- There's more. - It's huge.
(This time, it's vertically long.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Why is the cone so big? - We should put it there.
- Oh, my. - Goodness.
This is really amazing.
Once the batter is ready, we can make many kinds of dosa.
(Dosa, an Indian flatbread...)
(made with fermented rice and lentil batter)
(Cooked until thin and crispy)
We can make it like a cone, we can make it round,
and we can make it triangle.
And we can add the filling in it.
(Dosa: A South Indian staple with endless varieties)
Ghee roast is rolled into a cone.
(Ghee roast is cone-shaped!)
(For the family-sized dosa, 2 chefs roll it up together.)
This isn't for a normal family.
An extended family must come to finish it.
The portion is huge.
(Incredible in size)
- It's super long. - This is amazing.
- Gosh. - Really.
Does it actually exist?
(Is it really an authentic Indian vegetarian dish?)
(Enjoy!)
- Let's leave it there. - It's like someone's birthday.
Right?
- Unbelievable. - Really.
(Amazed)
- It's Harry Potter. - Try it on.
Those who are on social media would take...
- tons of photos here. - Totally.
This is unreal.
- It's... - We should name it giant dosa.
How do we dig into it?
- Coriander and tomatoes. - Cheese...
- Please tell us how to eat it. - Rip it, dip it, and eat.
You usually serve dosas with three different chutneys.
(Dosa is served with 3 sauces.)
- This one is coconut chutney. - Coconut.
Yes, the white-colored chutney is coconut.
(Rich and creamy, coconut chutney)
- This one is coriander chutney. - Coriander chutney.
(Fragrant and refreshing, coriander chutney)
- This one is tomato chutney. - Tomato chutney.
(Sweet and tangy with a spicy kick, tomato chutney)
And also sambar.
And also, we serve makhani sauce.
You can enjoy dosa with these dips.
(Dip the dosa into whichever sauce you'd like!)
(How's their first-ever dosa?)
(Crunchy)
(Her eyes widen.)
It's good.
It reminds me of salty jeonbyeong.
Is there something identical to this?
- It's giving me crepe vibes. - Totally.
It's good.
(A real dosa ASMR)
- This is delicious. - It has a kick.
It's similar to a crepe,
but it's much crunchier and saltier.
(The crispy texture and salty flavor keep you coming back for more.)
- Just right for Korean palates. - I come back to this one.
- It has a kick. - This is delicious.
(Topping the dosa with coconut chutney)
(Munching)
Even the coconut chutney is salty.
I thought it'd be sweet.
- It's still good. - Have you tried it?
(Kyoung Pyo, who wasn't interested in vegetarian food, tries it.)
The curry is actually good.
- Have you tried it? - It's really good.
It tastes of rich tomato curry,
but it's smooth, just like rose.
(Smooth makhani sauce with onion, tomato, and butter)
- It's actually good. - Just look at the variety.
- The many choices boost the meal. - Totally.
It's good. It's really good.
(A variety of sauces to choose from)
If you're on a diet, it'll legit... It'll really help you lose weight.
Did you say "legit?"
(What was that?)
- Ye Na. - Yes?
- Did you just say "legit?" - It'd legit help you.
(The world of dosa is remarkable in many ways.)
- There's more. - More?
We ordered one more dish.
(The dish served after dosa)
Tandoor-grilled...
- paneer... - Paneer and pineapple tikka.
(Paneer and pineapple tikka:)
(Indian cheese and pineapple marinated in...)
(yogurt and spices, grilled in a tandoor)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Tandoor...
(Vegan food with a smoky tandoor flavor)
- Is it cheese? - What is it?
I'm not sure if it's tofu or cheese.
- It's cheese. - I smell tofu.
It's cheese.
- Cheese? - Is it cheese?
(Nutty paneer with a subtle tang and spices)
Doesn't the "tandoori..."
in tandoori chicken mean the sauce?
- Isn't it how it's cooked? - Is it?
Possibly.
But it doesn't taste like the tandoori we're used to.
- Tandoori chicken... - Yes?
isn't usually this yellow.
It's giving off three-minute instant curry.
The color of tandoori is...
quite dark.
Let's try it, Jun Ha. Give it a taste.
Jumping the gun...
and saying it's instant curry is a bit...
Three-minute instant curry is good.
True.
You'll get attacked by both parties.
(3-minute instant curry and restaurant)
As a veteran, I think that was...
an inappropriate comment.
My apologies.
(Reflecting on himself)
- Pineapple? - It's cooked pineapple.
(Jae Seok tries a bit of it too.)
- But... - It's...
(Tangy)
- What's wrong? - It's the flavor...
Jae Seok hates the most.
Food with strong spices.
It's...
It's not for me.
You can't make such a face...
at the restaurant.
The owner will get offended by it.
- The thing is... - A veteran shouldn't do that.
- That little... - And right after you ate it.
As a pro, I...
- As a pro, I... - Do you agree?
- Yes. As a pro, - Of course.
I wasn't being professional.
- Apologies to the owner and Jun Ha. - It's okay.
They're making me uncomfortable.
The two are...
- Please save me. - It's the tension between the two.
(Going off on both sides)
But as for the dosa,
- everyone will like it. - That's why the owner...
- recommended it earlier. - Totally.
(The owner had a reason for recommending it.)
- If I were vegan, - Yes?
I would come and dine here.
The choices I have are...
Because there's a lot to choose from?
- There's a lot to choose from. - The menu has various vegan items.
Exactly, there's a variety.
It's here.
What's that?
(We have more food?)
- It's another dish. - Another one?
Onion pakora.
- It's not curry. - "Eat a lot?"
Eat a lot?
(Onion pakora, not "Eat a lot!")
- Onion. - Onion.
Onion.
- It's what BIBI ordered. - BIBI ordered the dish...
- The food is... - made with chickpea powder batter.
Correct.
- Onion. - It's what BIBI ordered.
BIBI ordered onion pakora.
Onion pakora.
(An Indian vegetarian delicacy, onion pakora)
(So, how does it taste?)
It's like deep-fried vegetables.
- Right? - Right.
When you go to snack stands and fritter places...
- Really? - Spicy deep-fried vegetables.
(A vegetable fritter with a hint of spice, onion pakora)
But the thing is, the sauces provided...
- are similar. - True.
All are served with three chutneys.
Coconut, tomato, and coriander.
With these,
I bet you could have 200 menu items.
- Right, because basic sauces are... - Right?
- provided like side dishes. - Exactly.
(Use the same sauce, and 200 menus are possible!)
Honestly, the dishes are quite similar.
- Just change the sauces. - Yes.
Exactly. The dishes have been slightly modified.
You can't say it's 200.
No offense, but are you here to boost this restaurant?
Really...
(Day 1, still adjusting)
I was...
- Two hundred... - What's up with you?
I don't think they should say it's 200 items.
Dishes derived from 20 base dishes.
You may have been cast yesterday, but give it your all.
(Having fun teasing Jun Ha)
- Please. - Okay.
Let's move to the next restaurant.
- Okay. - Let's compare at the next place.
- Let's do that. - I'm in.
(Indian vegetarian restaurant with 200 dishes)
(To the second restaurant that's hard to order)
I know this place.
How do you know this place?
I came here often in the past.
(Located on the street Jun Ha frequented)
Gosh, this area is really giving off...
(Where's the second place that's hard to order?)
Wait, this must be the place.
Is it?
Street food?
Street food sounds good!
The name is covered. It must be the place.
(Judging by the covered name, this must be the place.)
Don't you love street food, Jae Seok?
I totally do.
After having Indian food,
- A slightly spicy street food. - it's perfect.
- Time to settle with some spice. - I love street food.
(Second location: On-site reaction hint)
(Scribbling sounds)
(Is this right?)
(The resemblance is incredible.)
(Why is this snack stand hard to order?)
It definitely smells like a snack stand here.
This place is... Gosh.
My goodness, this is just perfect.
It's...
Jae Seok would love it.
- I'm loving it. - Goodness.
(What is this place that instantly won Jae Seok over?)
What an awesome menu.
I absolutely love street food.
(All the trusty street food classics are here.)
(There are also fusion dishes perfect for Gen Z.)
(Artwork throughout the shop makes this place stand out.)
What was the hint again?
Scribbling, and then,
- What's this? - "Is this right?"
It's...
I'm guessing you stick the drawing on here.
- What? - How cute.
So you can draw the food here.
(It's covered in food drawings.)
You must hand in a drawing to order.
(That's new.)
Seriously?
We have to draw the food we want to order here.
Pens and such are all here.
(Draw the food you'd like to order.)
Why would you draw to order?
That's wild.
- The theme is so cute. - It's adorable.
But those who are bad at drawing...
Exactly. Can't you just serve the food?
It's...
- This is quite inconvenient. - What...
(Taken aback)
If this is real, it's such a fun theme.
(Is this really a snack stand where you order by drawing?)
Shall we invite the owner over?
Excuse me!
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hi. - Nice to meet you.
We want to know what kind of snack stand this is.
This is a fusion snack stand with...
a special menu.
This is a restaurant with a special menu item...
where the customer's drawing is cooked as a dish.
(A restaurant where your drawing becomes food?)
As many foreigners come to tour this area,
I was looking for something fun.
Drawing has always been a hobby of mine.
It's a challenge menu created with a fun device...
called a live sketch.
(A challenge menu you order by drawing)
We have usual street foods.
Refer to today's ingredients written on the chalkboard...
and draw the menu you want.
We'll make it exactly as you drew it.
(My drawing comes to life as a special menu.)
The customers have fun.
By uploading it to social media voluntarily,
we're becoming known as a place where you can draw.
(Thanks to the customers, it became a popular spot in Itaewon.)
Sixth Sense crew, is this place real?
(This should be fun.)
I read the menu closely.
The special menu is ten dollars.
Combine today's ingredients well,
and you'll get a more delicious dish...
than the usual ones at a lower price.
(Get a tastier dish at a lower price than the regular menu.)
You could eat something worth 100 dollars if you're good at drawing.
- Totally. - Jun Ha is good at drawing.
Say that you have no idea what the drawing is.
Do you ask the customer,
or do you interpret it your own way?
- I never ask the customer. - Of course not, that's the theme.
I try to listen to and figure out the customer's heart.
The customer who orders that menu...
- even takes that into account. - Correct.
(The customers will enjoy the food even if it turns out differently.)
Let me give you a demonstration.
- Yes, show us. - Go ahead.
The owner said he normally draws in the restaurant,
so we'll get to see how good or bad he is.
We...
Pens are here.
We'll end up using them.
You're like the owner.
Take your time.
The customers love it.
It's like they switched.
- Let's say I'm drawing a carrot. - Carrot?
Nice, carrot.
It's helpful to capture its distinct feature.
- If I draw it like... - Anyone can tell it's a carrot.
Yes. If you draw a carrot which anyone can tell,
- it'll help out. - Right.
For now, the carrot...
(That's it?)
- Sir. - Sir?
We're not here to have carrots.
- Draw a dish. - Okay.
Exactly. Don't just do the bare minimum and walk away.
- Please put in some effort. - Right.
I like fish cakes.
- Fish cakes. - Fish cakes could be drawn like so.
It's perfect.
- Totally. - This is how you could draw a dish.
- Okay, we've got the gist. - After you draw it...
The machine detects it.
- Line up the corners. - Okay.
(Press the button.)
(Appearing on the monitor exactly as it is)
(The order has been placed.)
(Amazed)
- That's so cute. - Seriously?
It's awesome.
- My gosh. - Amazing.
(Everyone is blown away by the new technology.)
How about we start off with the special menu?
We could order food the convenient way.
Here's Mr. Grouchy.
Great.
It's tough.
(Now that it's time to draw...)
This is bad.
(Everyone finds it hard.)
(Thinking)
I'll start by drawing instant noodles!
(I'll start by drawing instant noodles!)
(Suddenly shouting at the kitchen)
- He must hear you from the kitchen. - Instant noodles...
I'm thinking Shin Ramyun!
(What a monkey he is.)
Shin Ramyun or...
I'm done.
- What is that? - I can guess.
- What is it? - Kimchi fried rice with eggs.
(Write the table number when ordering 85 Special Menu.)
- No, you're wrong. - What is it?
- Beef brisket doenjang stew or not? - For real?
- Is it beef brisket ramyun? - This is bad.
- Yes, you're right. - Beef brisket ramyun.
See? Nobody gets it if you don't say what it is.
(What Eun I drew was beef brisket ramyun.)
All right, as for me...
I'm going to write in "Shin."
No, no writing.
(No, no writing!)
- Why not? - That's not...
No, we were told not to write anything.
Why can't I write "Shin" in Chinese characters?
We can't write anything down.
(They're hilarious!)
Scan yours quickly, Jae Seok.
- I... - I'm going to scan...
mine and Jae Seok's.
(The owner must know that it's instant noodles.)
(Eun I's and Jae Seok's are being scanned.)
- Eun I's order has been placed. - I'm done with the drawing.
(Jae Seok's order has been placed.)
Jae Seok, this is...
I bet you'd get a large bowl of pickled radish.
He'll get it by the curly noodles.
- What if you get... - The curliness will give it away.
a large bowl of pickled radish?
BIBI is drawing it all realistically.
(Surprised)
- Anyone will get what it is. - Right?
Meringue, ice cream, and a cherry. Anyone can tell.
- You're good. - What a talent.
- A jack-of-all-trades. - Thank you.
It'd be mean if the owner didn't serve it as BIBI drew.
(BIBI's waffle ice cream has been ordered.)
- What are you drawing? - This?
It's a secret.
Are you still drawing, Senior Manager Jung?
(Senior Manager Jung is sweating and fully immersed.)
Jun Ha, you're great at drawing.
No way.
(Hard at work)
(How did Jun Ha's and Kyoung Pyo's drawings turn out?)
(Jun Ha, Kyoung Pyo)
- Kyoung Pyo's an artist. - Kyoung Pyo.
(Impressed)
Those are incredible.
This place is fun to come to...
- with friends. - Totally.
I'd love to bring my friends here if this place were real.
I know, right?
(A snack stand with plenty to enjoy for Gen Z)
- Everyone is good at drawing. - All of you are artists.
What do I do?
Ye Na, what's yours?
Mine is...
Ye Na...
- You might starve today. - Ye Na.
Nobody will get it even in "Family Entertainment."
(So, what is Ye Na's drawing?)
- Ye Na. - Yes?
- You're bad at drawing like me. - She gave it her all.
Don't get shocked by what's served.
Whatever is served, I'll devour it.
Ye Na.
(The kitchen has received the orders!)
(Spotted something on the shelf?)
(She pulls it out to take a closer look.)
This drawing is cheering me up.
- What is that? - Show me.
What is that? Where did you find it?
It's cheering me up.
- It was over there. - That...
These must be the customers' drawings. How cute.
(They look like drawings by other customers.)
I find this drawing really strange.
- This one. - It's weird.
What is that?
Plenty of people draw like this.
That's red bean bingsu.
You'd be served a loofah.
I'm probably not right,
but you can spot such drawings among them.
A customer came with his girlfriend.
- The girlfriend gave it her all. - She's enjoying it.
- But the boyfriend wasn't into it. - Right.
- The guy just draws sloppily. - "Let's just have..."
- "instant noodles and tteokbokki." - Exactly.
Don't draw if you don't want to.
It's...
(You scared me.)
- You scared me. - Totally.
You totally scared me.
If you didn't want to do it, tell me you didn't want to come.
- No, it's just that... - Gosh.
- No, it's not like that. - Why waste your talent here?
(She's still immersed.)
(Frustrated)
Really, you ruined it all.
(You're good.)
Really.
- Really. - The details were insane.
- She's like an annoyed girlfriend. - An annoyed girlfriend.
- Nice. - Totally.
An annoyed girlfriend.
What about you, CEO Song?
Give it a go. It's fun.
Try it.
Come on. Just once.
I'm already beat.
A person like Eun I drains me the most.
(The type to keep at it until the end)
- It's here. - It's here.
Let's see.
(Whose menu is served first?)
- If it's eggs... - Ta-da.
(A fried egg is visible.)
It's Eun I's.
(Eun I's drawing was topped with a fried egg.)
- Gosh. - It's this one.
- Enjoy. - An egg and...
- An egg and... - Pork.
Pork belly.
- Is this what you ordered? - No.
I wanted beef brisket ramyun.
- But... - The beef brisket wasn't obvious.
I understood Song Eun I's drawing as a pork belly rice bowl.
(It became a pork belly rice bowl.)
For the brown meat in the drawing,
I used tare sauce, which is often used in...
Japanese rice bowls.
It'll add to the meat's smokiness and umami.
(Adding smokiness and umami by using a torch)
After placing thinly sliced onions,
it's finished off with a fried egg and chives.
But it still looks good.
- Spicy stir-fried pork rice bowl. - It does look good.
(Pork belly rice bowl is actually better.)
Score!
- I got something much better. - It was...
A surprise like that would be interesting.
Right?
- During the delivery... - It's here.
What is it?
- It's here. - What is it?
(The menu is served to Jae Seok.)
- What is it? - Carbonara...
It's Jae Seok's dish.
- Sir, I... - It's carbonara.
- Sir, I... - It's udon noodles with bacon.
(Sir...)
Wait.
(Running away)
(Jae Seok desperately calls for the owner, but...)
Don't run away.
Did he just leave after serving the food?
Isn't it too...
(How funny.)
It's too different.
What's more, I only eat oil-based pasta.
Anyone can tell it's instant noodles.
But...
(The spicy instant noodles Jae Seok truly wanted...)
The owner served something better than the drawing.
- I wanted to say that. - Right?
To bring out the color of the yellow noodles Yu Jae Seok drew,
I made a creamy udon...
with rich heavy cream and milk.
(Jae Seok's instant noodles order)
(Failed)
- What's this? - Udon isn't Jae Seok's favorite.
I kept mentioning it was instant noodles.
(This is hilarious.)
In your face.
Isn't this saying, "Get out?"
(Isn't this saying, "Get out?")
I'm shocked.
It's fun.
- Such a situation actually happens. - Right?
- It sure is funny. - It's really funny.
- Yes, it's funny. - Right?
(Either way, let's taste it.)
How is it? How's the taste?
It's still good.
(That's a relief.)
It's really...
It's delicious.
(Laughing)
- Pork cutlet? - Who ordered pork cutlet?
- Pork cutlet? - He cooked it based on the drawing.
(Nobody ordered pork cutlet.)
- Oh, my gosh. - Is it Ye Na's?
- Amazing! - Pork cutlet.
(Serving it to Ye Na)
- Pork cutlet... - The color...
- topped with sweet potatoes. - Pork cutlet...
- It's topped with sweet potatoes. - It looks similar.
It's even better.
- Right? - Sir.
Ye Na, what did you draw?
It's a waffle with ice cream...
- on top. - That's a waffle.
A waffle.
(Ye Na's ice cream waffle...)
(turned into a jumbo pork cutlet.)
We interpreted Ye Na's drawing to be a pork cutlet.
On top of deep-fried pork cutlet,
deep-fried sweet potatoes were added to depict the circles on top.
(It's completely different from what she wanted.)
This looks good though. I like it.
- You like it? - Yes.
You end up eating more than you thought.
You're right.
I'll enjoy eating this.
(She quickly takes a bite.)
- Ye Na, is it delicious? - It's so good.
- Here it comes. - What's that?
- Here it comes. What is it? - I think that's mine.
- I think it's a wrong dish. - What is it?
It's bean sprouts dried pollack ramyeon.
- Bean sprouts and what? - Enjoy your food.
This isn't what I wanted.
- Bean sprouts... - There's clearly no brown thing...
- There's no meat here. - Was it on purpose?
(Kyoung Pyo's meat ramyeon...)
(Generous amount of brown meat)
- Dried pollack ramyeon. - Dried pollack ramyeon.
(It became bean sprouts dried pollack ramyeon.)
Out of all of ours, yours is the most similar to the drawing.
- That is true. - Yes.
(It still is ramyeon, after all.)
I don't enjoy seafood.
- You really don't? - No.
He put tons of shellfish. What a waste.
- You can't eat them? - I'll eat them.
Swap with mine, then. You can have mine...
- when mine is served. Swap. - Yes.
Shellfish smells incredible.
You're excited, Jun Ha. You'll eat with both hands.
(Slurping)
How does it taste?
It's so tasty.
- It's good, right? - This is crazy.
The food here is really good.
You could do this much, but...
they cooked like that.
An idea suddenly flashed in my mind.
- What is it? - It just came to me.
(Curious)
We all ordered the special menu,
but they're served very quickly.
What if the chefs...
from "Please Take Care of My Refrigerator..."
are doing the 15-minute cooking?
- They're doing it? - They're cooking really quickly,
- That could be the case. - and he just serves the food.
That could be the case.
Chef Kim Poong might suddenly appear.
Is Kim Poong really in there?
Poong?
I think yours is here.
- It's yours. - It's mine.
It's yours.
(Jun Ha's food is finally here.)
What is it?
- Ramyeon! - This is more to my taste.
- It's mine. - Ramyeon!
This is more to my taste.
- It looks like kimchi ramyeon. - Ramyeon...
- They made it correctly. - What is it?
- It's kimchi ramyeon. - Right?
- How is this kimchi? It's ham. - Just eat it.
- Sir. - Just...
(Jun Ha's ham ramyeon...)
(Two pieces of ham)
(It turned into kimchi ramyeon.)
For Jung Jun Ha's kimchi ramyeon,
I decided the rectangles he drew were kimchi.
I stir-fried it well in oil...
and made delicious kimchi ramyeon...
with curly noodles.
- Sir. - Just...
Just eat it.
Did you run out of ham? It says there...
I'm sorry, but you already had mine.
- You can swap. - I'll have this.
I'll have this.
(Jun Ha and Kyoung Pyo swap their dishes.)
This...
- This looks good. - This is delicious.
That looks tasty.
- Right? Would you like some? - Eat up.
(Kimchi ramyeon is really popular.)
- All that's left is BIBI's. - Yes, BIBI's.
- Here it is. - BIBI's.
It's exactly the same!
(Surprised)
This is what I wanted.
I did it!
(BIBI's menu is ice cream waffle.)
- I did it! - Was this what you wanted, Ye Na?
Exactly this.
(It's just like the drawing.)
The food is good here,
- but she mentioned Kim Poong. - Yes.
"Bunsik 85." Kian84.
He's close with Poong.
Kim Poong draws too.
Is there any word with "poong" in it?
"Landscape?"
(What caught Jae Seok's eye...)
(are the landscapes on the wall.)
(They're suspicious.)
Why are they hanging up those pictures there?
Is he really in there?
(Jae Seok's guess: The landscapes are hints to Kim Poong?)
But this...
This is a self-employed small restaurant.
Is this pricing really right?
Isn't ten dollars great?
If he does business like this, it won't last long.
The economy is struggling as is.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Are you here to film "Baek Jong Won's Alley Restaurant?"
- You're giving them a solution. - Why do you keep...
providing solutions to all the restaurants?
I wasn't giving a solution. Look at the owner.
He's either a producer or an assistant director.
He must've come here in the midst of editing.
What's the director's name?
He looks like a Nam Cheol. Nam Cheol!
Kim Nam... Mr. Nam Cheol!
"Mr. Nam Cheol."
- Ye Na. - Yes?
It's been a few hours...
- since you've met Jun Ha. - Yes.
What kind of person do you think he is?
Be honest.
I think he'll have a carefree life.
(Laughing)
(Ye Na's innocent answer)
(Smiling)
I do have a carefree life.
Nothing uncomfortable.
You're like my dad.
- In what way? - Initially, he complained so much.
"Why do I need to do this?"
But when the food came out, he finished the whole thing.
You're right.
(Clean)
- "It's so good." - "My gosh."
- "How is it so good?" - "How is it so good?"
That's right.
- Shall we go? - Let's go.
Mr. Nam Cheol, we're off.
"Nam Cheol."
Anyway, out of the two,
that's the one.
The 200 dishes place was very suspicious,
but compared to the one just now, the first place is pretty okay.
When you consider...
the feasibility of the restaurant cost-wise,
with the turnover rate and so on,
- you can tell what's fake. - Yes, something like that.
And street food...
- needs high turnover rate. - Exactly.
- That's what street food is about. - That's the merit.
Drawing, scanning,
and waiting for the food took some time.
Right.
(The whole process took a long time.)
We...
We're looking for one fake place, right?
- Yes. - Are you finding the real place?
Well...
(Intimidated)
We're looking for one fake place?
You could've asked Jae Seok.
Why did you turn around uncomfortably and ask me?
(Snorts)
He isn't kind.
(That's his true feeling.)
He even said this now.
(Looking far ahead)
I'm being accompanied by Senior Manager Jung.
Exactly.
The Muhan Company concept continues in our daily lives too.
You're right.
(Senior Manager Jung's first day at Sixth Sense Company)
- Now... - It's hard.
I've been working with him all this while.
It must be tough for you too.
What do you think, Senior Manager Jung?
(Manager Yu switches to work mode right away.)
I think so too. I think you're right.
I don't need to voice out my opinion.
Do you think so?
Yes, of course.
(Once a senior manager, forever a senior manager)
The way he speaks...
sparked nostalgia.
- Nostalgia. - It hit me.
It goes as far as being nostalgic?
Nostalgia.
Ye Na, how old were you when "Infinity Challenge" aired?
- Second year in elementary school? - Second year in elementary school?
- I think so. - Second year in elementary school.
"Maljuk Street?"
- Maljuk Street? - "Once Upon a Time in High School."
- It's Maljuk Street. - We're at Maljuk Street.
Amazing.
- This is Maljuk Street? - Yes, this is Maljuk Street.
This is where they used to feed horses.
That's why it's "maljuk."
(The street where they fed porridge to horses and let them rest)
(It's where "Once Upon a Time in High School" was based on.)
Let's go.
(Where's the restaurant that is hard to order?)
This is the place?
(They spot it as soon as they get out of the car.)
It's this place?
Coffee?
It's a cafe.
I'm glad it's not another meal.
(It's dessert this time!)
"Coffee roastery, hand drip coffee."
(The last place on Maljuk Street...)
(is a hand drip coffee shop?)
(Tapping)
(A sound of a machine?)
(What? Is it mind reading?)
(Why is this place hard to order?)
Let's...
(Entering carefully)
- It's nice. - Hello.
- It's nice in here. - Hello.
My gosh.
- It looks legit. - Yes.
Is it a research lab?
(When you open the door,)
(the harmony of wood and metal welcomes you.)
What place is this?
(The harmony of wood and metal welcomes you.)
Here's the menu. "Hand drip coffee, cafe latte..."
(The menu is that of a cafe.)
There are only four menu items.
There's a capsule.
Do we get to choose coffee beans?
(There are capsules in the middle of the cafe?)
(The table in the middle next to the counter)
They must be different types of coffee beans.
(And a tablet with its purpose unknown?)
Look at this. This must be what the tapping sound was about.
- I see. - I see.
(The tablet makes the same sound as the cassette hint.)
- Shall we have a seat? - Yes.
Here.
Let's call the owner over.
- Sir. - Sir.
He must be the owner.
- Hello. This way. - Hello.
- He looks like he'd make coffee. - Coffee.
- He's dandy. - He has the vibe.
Welcome to my shop.
I'm a foreigner, so...
Is it okay to speak in English?
- Yes. - Yes.
Of course.
(The interpreter appears.)
He's a foreigner?
Yes, I'm from Japan.
(No wonder!)
Really?
(The second foreign owner of the day!)
So this cafe is hard to order?
Yes, so, our cafe is a little bit unique.
- Yes. - Instead of having a fixed menu,
everybody uses AI...
to create their own coffee blend.
Everybody will get their own, different coffee.
(Making my own coffee using AI?)
Did you make coffee before this?
Actually, I got married to a Korean wife.
I moved to Korea,
but at that time, I was not working in coffee.
I worked in IT...
industry for ten years.
- It makes sense. - He looks like he worked in IT.
Exactly.
- It makes perfect sense. - AI came out...
We should try the coffee...
you recommend.
- We can customize our coffee? - Yes.
- I can make my own flavor. - Yes.
Jun Ha, go first.
(Jun Ha orders first.)
Let me give you a little explanation.
He'd like to explain.
There are three ways you can make a unique blend.
So you can choose those flavors,
or you can choose your MBTI.
- They have all the MBTI types. - Yes.
You can choose your mood and what you're feeling like.
Second is typing free text.
(Any sentence describing your taste or mood)
And the third one is by taking a selfie of your face.
And AI will read that emotion.
(AI will analyze your emotions from your face.)
The AI will recommend four different capsules.
Four different coffee beans out of the ten we have.
So the customers will pick those four capsules...
and bring that to the barista to get the coffee brewed.
(Bring it to the owner!)
This is so fascinating.
It's so interesting.
(It suits the Gen Z's taste.)
Since Manager Yu told me to go first...
Try it, Senior Manager Jung.
- Okay. - I'll try.
I like peach.
And acidity.
My MBTI is ESFP.
(Senior Manager Jung's taste in coffee)
And mood.
This... My first date with Sixth Sense.
(Peach, acidity, ESFP, first date)
(He chose his keywords.)
Okay? Complete?
- Yes, complete. - Yes.
He understands Korean.
No, a bit.
Of course he understands "complete." That's English.
No, I think he's Korean.
Because his wife is Korean.
His wife is Korean, but he also understands everything.
- The result is out. - What does it say?
- It's like... - What does it say?
- He understands everything. - The result is out.
(The result is out already.)
- What does it say? - It's like a chatbot program.
(The AI generates the result like a chatbot program.)
"Peach scent, acidity, and fluttering first date."
It explains for you.
(The combination of coffee beans, 1 Number 2, 1 Number 3, 2 Number 4s)
(Explanation about the coffee taste)
(Lemon lime, pineapple, bergamot, orange blossom)
One Number Two, one Number Three, and two Number Fours.
- That's your coffee. - That's your...
That's Jung Jun Ha's coffee.
(Coffee customized for Senior Manager Jung is ready.)
You should try next, CEO Song.
Shall I?
(Please place your orders.)
- This is so... - Jasmine.
- Jasmine. - And...
It will generate coffee for you based on your face, right?
I think so.
(Eun I takes a selfie.)
It's analyzing my vibe.
(The AI is analyzing the members.)
What does it say?
(Curious)
"True happiness" is 66 percent.
"Energetic confidence" is 20 percent.
"The impact of lack of sleep" is ten percent.
"Mild anxiety" is four percent.
(It breaks down the analysis into percentages.)
"The illusion that today will be different," 0.001 percent.
Maybe this means I can't guess right today.
This is so fun.
- This is incredible. - This...
- It's perfect for a date. - Right.
(The AI has captured the members' hearts.)
(Ye Na's recipe, Eun I's recipe)
"Take a selfie."
(BIBI takes a selfie to order.)
(Take a picture.)
(Making a pretty face expression)
(Analyzing the vibe)
Cute.
"Happiness full of a wide smile."
"Light curiosity."
What does "taken aback because he's so handsome" mean?
Oh! I told Kyoung Pyo today that he was handsome.
(Today morning)
(You look gorgeous.)
(Today morning, BIBI complimented Kyoung Pyo's looks.)
And it says here, "taken aback because he's so handsome."
- "Looking a bit tired." - It says like this.
- It even shows something like that? - Yes.
"Taken aback because he's so handsome."
Good for you.
(The AI even knows what happened today?)
(Suspicious)
(Is this really an AI cafe?)
But why does...
"today will be different" get on my nerves so much?
"The illusion that today will be different."
That sentence gets on my nerves.
Now that I think about it, you're right.
It sounds like it's teasing us...
- when I think about it. - Yes.
- It feels bad. - Right.
"The illusion that today..."
- "will be different." - You're right.
(It's got to be the staff.)
Someone might be observing us,
and the staff members might have controlled the system.
(Are the AI answers controlled by the staff?)
But the owner is an expert.
He is.
He's very much accustomed to this shop.
The ice is added evenly.
(The owner looks like a perfect coffee expert.)
The amount is perfect.
- You're right. - This...
The owner here...
Look at him removing the foams.
- He is used to... - He's an expert.
He's used to this.
- Foams and ice. - All the settings...
It's hard to do that from practice alone.
Look at him removing foams and ice shards.
- I'm talking! - I apologize.
- Senior Manager Jung! - Gosh, my ears.
I'm talking.
(Frustrated)
- I'm sorry. - I saw this coming.
- I saw this coming. - It's Muhan Company.
We're watching a live show of Muhan Company.
They're here to perform live.
We do a touring performance on tvN.
A Muhan Company tour.
It's so funny. This has been so long.
- Right? - Yes.
(You only scold me.)
They're ready. Jun Ha...
For you.
This is mine.
- And Ye Na. - This is...
- Yes. - Thank you.
With CEO Song. I'm curious about the taste.
(Even though I got scolded, I should smell the coffee.)
No way.
- How is it? - It smells like juice.
It doesn't smell like coffee. Is it not coffee?
- It smells like juice? - Yes.
Can I smell it?
(Sniffing)
- You're right. - Right?
(The customized coffee smells different.)
- Since they're mixed... - It really does.
- It smells like juice. - The scent...
(Jasmine night: A night of jasmine petals in mango yogurt)
They all have different colors.
Mine has a peach color.
You're right.
(The taste and scent are all very different.)
I'm excited.
- This is fascinating. - I like it.
(Taking a sip)
- This is acidic. - Is it very acidic?
- Not too strong. - It's just nice. I like it.
(The acidity is perfect for Kyoung Pyo.)
This place is incredible.
I agree. Can I try? You can try mine too.
(They can feel joy by trying others' coffees too.)
- It's... It's amazing, right? - It's nice.
It's so sweet and fragrant.
(Ye Na's coffee is full of sweet mango scent.)
- It's so good. - Really?
It even suits Jae Seok's taste when he's so picky.
(Everyone is in love with the customized coffee.)
It's tasty.
If this place is real, it's worth visiting.
- I agree. - It's so...
This has to be an actual place.
This is real. You can't fake this.
(The expert's skill cannot be faked. Is this place real?)
How much is one cup?
Five dollars?
- It's cheap. - It's cheap.
It's five dollars?
(Hand drip coffee, 5 dollars)
(It's cheap for customized coffee.)
- Is it 5 dollars? - Yes, everything is 5 dollars.
See? He's good at Korean.
(See? He's good at Korean.)
Gwang Seob!
- "Gwang Seob." - It's five dollars.
(Gwang Seob)
Senior Manager Jung.
- I'm sorry. - Why do you keep...
I think he's Korean.
(I really think he's Korean.)
"Gwang Seob."
(Is this place fake? Is he actually good at Korean?)
What if in the answer video, he says,
"Hello, I'm Gwang Seob."
- "You guys got fooled." - My goodness.
We can't have that.
If we get this wrong,
- we'll have a penalty. - Right.
- Exactly. - For today's penalty,
let me grab your mouth.
But Ye Na.
(He didn't hear it.)
What did you say?
For today's penalty, let me grab your mouth.
He wants to grab your mouth.
- Like this. - Good.
Can I smack your head?
(I can't lose.)
(Choking)
- The back of his head? - Yes.
That's the word.
The back of his head.
(Will he put the back of his head on the line?)
Smack.
- Shall we leave for now? - I can't decide.
(Cafe ordered by AI)
Which do you think is fake?
Okay.
I really can't tell this time.
I think it's the second one.
Scan the drawings.
The whole process is very tedious.
(When you draw the menu you want,)
(it turns into a real dish?)
(Sir, I...)
(It's way too different.)
(The dish is different from what you imagined.)
(But it looks delicious.)
(A dish beyond your imagination is served.)
(But it's too tedious to run a restaurant like this.)
(No. 2: The restaurant ordered by drawing)
The thing is, the second place...
had drawing tools that were in too good shape.
If they were used a lot,
- they should show signs of wear. - Exactly.
- That's true. - He has a point.
You really catch the details.
Okay. So everyone thinks the second one is fake?
- Yes. - It's the second place.
All right. Then we have no choice.
Even if we get a penalty, we should go with the second one.
But...
- Why? - Do you have a different opinion?
Someone might have a different view.
Don't keep getting swept along.
Feel free to speak up, Manager Yu.
I told you. I think it's the second one.
Then why do you keep bringing up the third place?
We've been backstabbed a few times,
firmly believing it was real.
Then you should go with number three.
- But number 3... - I'll go with number 2.
- That's not how you do this. - That's not what I mean.
- That's not it. - I'm saying we should have a match.
A match between you and me.
(A match just between the two?)
We will go with number two as a team, but...
I'm sticking with number two.
- Then I'll go with number one. - Okay. Good.
- I see. - Number one?
If I win, I'll stretch your lips.
- Like this. - Okay. Good.
Then, if I win...
You picked number 1. If the answer is number 2,
you'll say, "Boss, I will never mess with you again."
"I'll get going now."
You say this and bow at 90 degrees.
(He should bow at 90 degrees and walk off.)
(Chuckling)
- That's a neat way to exit. - I know.
What if Jun Ha wins?
- If I win... - He will stretch my lips.
- Your lips. - That's it.
I'm not just stretching his lips.
"Boss, you're really..."
- "You are..." - No, you can't add that now.
(That's not allowed.)
Is it over already?
It's a done deal. It's only the lips.
Can't I get an extra shot?
- No, you can't. - "An extra shot?"
You can't add the speech.
But number one did seem strange.
I think it is an Indian restaurant,
- That's right. - but I don't think...
- they have 200 menu items. - Exactly.
(We have...)
(200 menu items!)
(A restaurant with 200 vegetarian menu items)
(An unrealistic number of dishes, endless no matter how much you flip)
(Is this place fake?)
(Can they cover unit costs with 200 menu items?)
(Even the welcome performance feels even faker.)
(No. 1: Indian vegetarian restaurant with 200 dishes)
Are you going with number one?
Wait. Come to think of it,
number 2 was fake in Episode 1.
Episode 2's answer was also number 2.
Could it be number 2 in Episode 3 too?
- In Episode 3... - Were all the answers number 2?
- You're right. - The second place was fake.
This is driving me crazy.
Really? The answer was number two every time?
The production crew would never do that.
Number one is suspicious,
- but number two is more suspicious. - I see.
- I really don't know. - This is hard.
I have no idea.
We talked a lot on the way,
and there was an opinion to go with number two...
without stalling.
Please.
Actually, we all agreed to go with number two,
but in my heart, I feel like it's number one.
Right. Number one is suspicious.
Today, it's either number 1 or number 2.
- BIBI, you think it's number 2. - I think it's number 2.
BIBI's gut feeling has been sharp.
Then since BIBI's pick is number two...
- I worried that you'd say this. - But...
- This is Episode Three, right? - Let's just go with it.
- It's Episode 3. - Episode 3.
(Shaking her legs)
If we don't get it right today, it's consecutive misses,
- so we will get a penalty. - There will be a penalty.
The production crew wouldn't make it number 2 3 times in a row.
(It can't be number 2 3 times in a row.)
All right.
Our choice is number two.
Let's see if you can get it right today.
Please show us.
(Ordering difficulty: Five stars)
(What are we supposed to do?)
(Nothing went their way.)
- Please. - Why Can't You Order?
All right. Please let it be right.
- Please. - Please.
- Please let it be right. - Please.
Please.
(Desperate)
- Please. - Please.
(Which is the only fake place?)
- It can't possibly be number three. - No. Please.
Why do I feel like we got it wrong? The production crew looks happy.
I know.
(Unusually serious)
(Which is the only fake place?)
Why do I feel like we got it wrong? The production crew looks happy.
I know.
(Unusually serious)
(Which is the only fake place?)
Which is it?
Which one?
Number two!
(No. 2 Restaurant Ordered by Drawing is fake.)
(We got it right.)
(Yes!)
- Number 2! - Number 2!
(Yes, it's No. 2!)
Number two!
(This is it!)
(Joy at its max)
- Yes! - We got it right.
(And there's one person...)
(who is looking grim.)
Right. I thought so.
We did it.
(Forcing himself to smile)
I'm so relieved.
- See? I told you it was number two. - That's right.
Was it Kim Poong? It wasn't him?
(Utterly thrilled)
The production crew really sticks to their guns.
They went with number two all the way.
It was so thrilling.
That was really thrilling.
- I see. - Seriously...
(How on earth was this place created?)
- It really looked legit, though. - Totally.
(The owner's true identity)
Hello. I'm...
not the owner of Bunsik 85,
a tricky place to order...
where food comes out the way you draw it.
(That's not who I am.)
- I'm not the owner. - Okay.
Is he a webtoon artist?
Who is he?
I'm a man who draws lines in a different way.
I'm a plastic surgeon specializing in double eyelid surgery,
- Jun Hui Chang. - What?
(What?)
This is hilarious.
- It's so funny. - Why would he go this far?
- But... - The owner...
Is he a plastic surgeon?
I have 16 years of experience in plastic surgery.
Why is a doctor doing this?
I draw eye anatomy quite a lot...
for precise patient consults.
(Master of drawing eyes)
- He draws really well. - They found the right person.
How did they cast him?
- I couldn't imagine it. - He draws...
surgical reviews himself.
That makes him trust even more.
(They are the doctor's drawings.)
It aligned with what I do best,
so I had fun preparing for this.
- He drew all this! - That's great.
- He's good at drawing. - It's unbelievable.
(Now that the fake owner is ready...)
Then what is this space?
- Was it a restaurant? - An ordinary restaurant?
(Breathing Sixth Sense's life into it!)
They did this?
- They built it themselves. - Right.
- That must have been tough. - They worked so hard.
It seems like the doctor drew the menu himself.
(The monitor and scanner are installed.)
I really like this idea.
I know. It would be great if there were a place like this.
(Dishes turning your imagination into reality)
Who brought this to life?
(Who made these dishes?)
Who cooked this in the kitchen?
Did they have Kim Poong in the kitchen or not?
(Those who took the drawn orders in the kitchen are...)
Who was it?
- They were kids? - I think...
this is definitely noodles.
- What? - What?
They were kids?
Is it something like cold buckwheat noodles?
I think it's a noodle dish.
Cream udon?
Cream udon? That sounds good.
I'm Park Eun Chong, and I'm 13 years old.
I'm 11 years old.
They're so adorable.
I know him!
- What? - Who?
(Who are the kids in the kitchen?)
(The winner of the "Finding Genius" Culinary King Contest)
- Seriously? - Really?
It's been about a year and a half since I started cooking.
(Knife skills are a given.)
(They've mastered a variety of dishes.)
(The little chefs)
The food we ate today was cooked by those little chefs?
No wonder it suited my palate.
- It was so delicious. - It was really tasty.
(Little Chefs' Mission: Cook from random drawings!)
Adults would figure it out right away.
- Right. - Sure.
It took kids' imagination...
- to pull off dishes like that. - Right.
(The members' drawn orders)
(They interpreted them with their innocent perspectives.)
- Bean sprout ramyeon? - Okay.
They really cook well.
I'm so proud of them.
(B-Side)
- What? - What?
(The places you visited)
- Where was something like that? - Where?
(The people you met)
(Today's B-Side that passed by them)
What was it?
- Where? - Where was it?
- What? - What?
Where was it?
I didn't see anything.
Where?
(The 3 places they visited today)
(Indian vegetarian restaurant with 200 dishes,)
(restaurant ordered by drawing, AI-curated cafe)
- Number 2 was fake. - Number 2.
- Right. - Number two.
- What about number two? - Two?
Was there something with two?
Where was it?
(Today's answer: 2)
(There were 22 instances of 2 in all!)
Were there that many twos?
Two?
Where?
We should've looked closely.
(No. 2, the fake restaurant)
(The landscape painting?)
(The landscape paintings were hanging on the wall.)
The paintings!
- It's two! - That's right!
(The landscape suspected as a clue about Kim Poong is...)
(a trail shaped like 2 inside the painting.)
(The trail is shaped like a 2.)
(Jaw-dropping)
I did think the painting was odd.
Seriously. I never thought they'd go this far.
(The number that appeared before the Sixth Sense members all day)
- Two? - When?
(Did you spot it?)
Aren't they our production crew?
(Crew members wearing number 2 jerseys and caps)
(They're standing right in front of them even now.)
What...
(The foot of the candle couldn't be darker than this.)
That's right!
- What... - The clock was set to 2pm?
(A clock set to 2pm)
(A calendar bizarrely set to the 22)
- I saw that. - I thought it was strange.
(The wi-fi password is 22EEee.)
You talked about it!
(Ye Na, try reading this out loud.)
(About 30 minutes ago, at the 3rd place)
It's 22EEee.
(Pointing a finger and even making a V)
(These two read it out loud.)
We really saw it all.
(Even on the fake restaurant's menu)
- Even on the menu? - My goodness.
(A number 2 pattern was softly placed.)
I got goosebumps!
- Unbelievable. - It gives me goosebumps.
They are really scary.
(And there's something that's always mentioned with 2.)
(Hong Jin Ho?)
Jin Ho is always in second place.
- Oh, right. - Was he there?
(Was there something like that?)
(Yes, there was.)
(Eternal 2nd place, the symbol of 2)
(They passed right by without noticing at all.)
It was number two.
They hid so many, yet we missed them completely.
(And do you remember?)
- What? - What is it now?
(Indian vegetarian restaurant with 200 dishes)
(The Bollywood performance prepared by the restaurant owner)
- Right. - What?
There was number two again?
Where?
What is this?
"Number do naqli."
(It means...)
(Number 2 is fake.)
- Seriously? - What?
(Shocked)
(The B-Side was blatantly hidden.)
How would we find out when we didn't know Hindi?
"Number do naqli?"
Sixth Sense members, this place is fake.
(No. 2 Restaurant Ordered by Drawing is fake.)
Thank you, Doctor.
He went through a lot.
I'm glad that we got it right,
but this is really shocking.
Did you invite me as a guest just because I have a snaggletooth?
Because tooth sounds like two?
- And him with crooked teeth. - By the way...
You should get the penalty now.
- Now... - Oh, right.
- That was that, and... - Right. We're moving on.
"Boss Jae Seok, I'm sorry that I messed with you."
Boss Jae Seok.
- Bow down even lower. - Okay.
Boss Jae Seok. I won't act up again.
I will watch my tongue.
I won't mess with you again.
I'll get going then.
All right.
Thank you for today.
(The beautiful departure of Senior Manager Jung,)
(accepting his defeat)
Is he really leaving like that?
(Kingdom of Sixth Sense in Mukho)
(A rising mecca for Gen Z)
(They're here to disrupt the Sixth Sense ecosystem.)
(Mukho's Predators, Lee Seon Min and Tzuyang)
(Leaping in joy)
(Do you usually find it hard to eat?)
(Predator Tzuyang Alert)
(At this rate, we won't get to eat.)
(The 5-on-1 showdown begins.)
(Checking the predator's current status)
(About 12 percent?)
(The Sixth Sense members are knocked out.)
(Predator Seon Min is playing on sheer instinct.)
(This really feels like Naples.)
(- Have you even been to Naples?) - No.
(His gut feeling doesn't look too sharp.)
(Don't just say random things, mister!)
(Usually, they give you scissors.)
(The owner seems a bit clumsy.)
(Herbivore Seon Min is oblivious to what's right under his nose.)
(Another fake place...)
(to uncover in Mukho?)
Today, let's just...
(Forget the fake or whatever today.)
(Just enjoying Mukho)